[Music]
okay so we are going to inject you with
enough propol to temporarily kill you
but then we'll bring you back with
adrenaline so you don't have any up up
up up no spoilers no spoilers and one
more thing you're not going to sue us
are you oh no litigation is for the
middle class as me you're going to love
dying it's hilarious it's like being
John malovich but you don't have to got
a jersey as long as I can discover the
first line of my squar play I'm down for
whatevs okay here we go bar
[Music]
bar
hello Dr Todds
oh a
door oh hey
man am I supposed to be afraid of you I
don't think so I'm just like hanging and
banging I like to come to a flatlining
universe cuz like it just helps me
concentrate on writing my scrm play
honestly it's like really exciting to
meet a fellow writer like I don't want
to like geek out on you but like I'm a
fern and I'm just like cheers oh my God
I feel like what we're trying to do is
like stand on the shoulders of JS like
turn Turner musar saer Hearn brother
starbo fure oh my God I love der
fure do you want to come in and like
chill out cheers I would love to yeah
that's one of the main challenges to
writing the scr play it needs to be
funny right away yeah it's got to be
funny but it also has to like grab you
yeah I love story but then I'm also like
I love character I just feel like that
first line in scrm playay people are
gonna be like oh look at that first line
like wild I think we should take a bar I
feel like we've done a lot of good work
and I think we don't want to get burned
out so like let's just Chiller what do
you want to do I don't know do you want
to just like yank each other off to
comparsion
[Music]
Dolphin oh what are you doing to me it's
like a Doppel gang bang isn't it stop
Bing like such a little dick and jack me
off you little
give me a pen and paper I just
wrote the first line of my screenplay
pen and paper please the writer's block
is over the writer's block is over um
Aspen I don't know how to tell you this
but uh Wendy is
[Music]
dead fade
in
yeah